A Guide to the Richmond (Va.) Office of the City Engineer, Records, 1809-1975
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Architectural drawings and plans, 1809-1975.
  - Park - City of Richmond, Va. / Plot of the Corner at Bank and 9th. Sts. / and a part of the Capitol Square / Showing present position of curbs gates and fences / and the proposed changes, 19-D-1, 1908, Dimensions: 27-1/2 x 35 in. - 70 x 89 cm.; Scale: 1" = 10'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
  - Park - City of Richmond, Va. / Plan / Walkways and Steps on Peninsular / in Lake at Wm. Byrd Park, 34-B-4, 1908, Dimensions: 26 x 23-1/4 in. - 66 x 59 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: India ink, red ink, and blue ink on linen; Sheets: 2 (Folder 38)
  - Park - Plat of Teenie Douglass' property on the West side of Pine Street, 36-C-2, 1908, Dimensions: 8-3/4 x 12 in. - 22 x 30 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 44)
  - Park - Plan of Public Comfort Station / Under Park-Keeper's Office at / Jefferson Park, 43-B-2, 1909, Dimensions: 22-3/4 x 25-1/4 in. - 58 x 64 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Fontaine Jones Asst. Engr. Del.
  - Park - City of Richmond Va. / Plans for Swings and Horizontal / and Parallel Bars / Williamsburg Ave. Playgrounds, 48-B-2, 1909, Dimensions: 17-3/4 x 24-3/4 in. - 45 x 63 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1/2'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
    Drawn By: City Eng'r's Office / Fontaine Jones / Asst. Engr.
  - Park - Plan of Base and Basin for Fountain / to be Erected at Chimborazo Park, 47-B-2a, 1909, Dimensions: 25-1/2 x 31 in. - 65 x 79 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 39)
  - Park - Plan of / Tool House / for / Keeper of Grass Plot / on / Monument Avenue, 42-B-2, 1909, Dimensions: 18-1/2 x 32-1/2 in. - 47 x 82 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
  - Park - Plan of Fountain Basin and Walk / and Fence Around Same at / Chimborazo Park, 47-B-2, 1910, Dimensions: 16-3/4 x 20-3/4 in. - 43 x 53 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 39)
    Drawn By: City Eng's Office / Richmond, Va. / Fontaine Jones / Asst. Engr.
  - Park - Plan of Granolithic Work Around Spring / at Wm. Byrd Park, 57-B-2, 1910, Dimensions: 19-3/4 x 30-1/4 in. - 50 x 77 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
  - Park - City of Richmond, Va. / Map of Part of Idlewood Park / Showing Present and Proposed Location of / Davis Avenue / and Certain Changes to be made in Buildings, 67-A-2, 1910, Dimensions: 16-1/2 x 4 in. - 42 x 114 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
  - Park - Jos. Bryan Park Dam / Plans for Splash Boards for Spillway, 58-A-1, 1911, Dimensions: 16-3/4 x 27-1/4 in. - 43 x 70 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 36)
  - Park - City of Richmond Va. / Jos. Bryan Memorial Park / Profile, Cross-Sections and / Plans of Dam, 41-B-3a, 1911, Dimensions: 25-3/4 x 37-1/2 in. - 65 x 95 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 36)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Fontaine Jones / Asst. Engineer
  - Park - Keepers House at Bryan Park / Henrico County - Virginia, [No file number], 1911, Dimensions: 32 x 19-1/2 in. - 81 x 50 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 3 (Folder 36)
    Drawn By: Carneal & Johnston / Architects and Engineers / Richmond, Virginia
  - Park - City of Richmond Va. / Plans of dam / at / Jos. Bryan Memorial Park, 41-B-3, 1911, Dimensions: 21-1/4 x 40 in. - 54x 102 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 36)
    Drawn By: City Engr's Office / Fontaine Jones / Asst. Engineer
  - Park - Marshall Square / Public Comfort Station & Park Keepers House / Plan for Enlarging & Remodeling Present Building, 45-B-3, 1911, Dimensions: 22-1/2 x 31 in. - 57 x 79 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
  - Park - Plat of Part of the Plan of 'Belvideria' / Adjacent to Riverside Park / Showing Lots 25, 26, and 27 to be Acquired for / Enlargement of Park, 36-C-2, 1911, Dimensions: 12-3/4 x 19-1/2 in. - 32 x 50 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 44)
  - Park - Jos. Bryan Park / map of Location, Plans & Profile of / Proposed Wing Walls and Road Change, 50-C-2, 1912, Dimensions: 22 x 19-1/2 in. - 56 x 49 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
  - Park - Entrance Arch / Joseph Bryan Park / Henrico County - Virginia, 38-A-6, 1912, Dimensions: 21-3/4 x 22-1/2 in. - 55 x 57 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: 1 blueprint with attached letter, 1 diazo print; Sheets: 2 (Folder 36)
  - Park - City of Richmond, Va. / Map of Properties in Wm. Byrd Park / Owned by / The William Byrd Realty Corporation & Stanhope Bolling, 44-C-2a, 1912, Dimensions: 19-1/2 x 29 in. - 50 x 74 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink and pencil notations on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
  - Park - Map of Property in the Confines of Wm. Byrd Park West of Chestnut Road, 44-C-2, 1912, Dimensions: 21-1/2 x 26 in. - 53 x 66 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
  - Park - City of Richmond Va. / William Byrd Park / Proposed Changes to Roadway Leading to / Davis Ave. and Beverly Street, 45-C-2, 1912, Dimensions: 23 x 40 in. - 58 x 102 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink and blue ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
    Drawn By: Office of City Eng'r / Richmond, Va.
  - Park - Chart of Washington Square Washington Ward / Showing Plan for Grading, 47-C-2, 1912, Dimensions: 17-3/4 x 23 in. - 45 x 59 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: Pencil and India ink on graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 42)
    Drawn By: City Eng'r Office / Richmond, Va.
  - Park - Sketch of a Portion of Chimborazo Park / Showing Cracks on South & Southwest / Slopes / Caused by Rains of Friday Mar. 15th & Sat. 23rd., 48-C-2, 1912, Dimensions: 15 x 23 in - 38 x 58 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: Pricking, pencil, India ink, and red ink on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 39)
  - Park - Sketch of a Portion of / Chimboraza [sic] Park / in the Vicinity of Nos. 3305, 3307 & 3309 / East Main Street / Showing Slips caused by the Rains of / March 15th & 23rd 1912, 48-C-2, 1912, Dimensions: 20-1/4 x 24 in. - 51 x 61 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 39)
  - Park - Wm. Byrd Park / Map / Shield's Grove and Lake / Showing Contours and General Plan of Impr't, 52-B-2, 1912, Dimensions: 16 x 29-1/2 in. - 41 x 75 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: 1 pencil, India ink, and colored inks on heavy paper, 1 pencil, India ink, and blue ink on linen; Sheets: 2 (Folder 37)
  - Park - Map of a Portion of Wm. Byrd Park Adjacent / to Reservoir Showing Present & Proposed / Change in Line of Park Roadway, 59-A-1, 1912, Dimensions: 16-1/2 x 27-1/2 in. - 42 x 70 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 37)
    Drawn By: City Engineers Office - Richmond, Va.
  - Park - [Elevation and plan of gates for Joseph Bryan Park], 10825-B-3, 1912, Dimensions: 14-3/4 x 23-3/4 in. - 38 x 61 cm.; Scale: 1" = 3'; Media: Blueprint with pencil notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 36)
  - Park - Map of a Portion of Wm. Byrd Park / Adjacent to the Reservoir / Showing Present Line and Proposed Change, 59-C-2, 1913, Dimensions: 22 x 44 in. - 56 x 112 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: piiol; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
  - Park - Plan of the / S. E. Cor. 9th & Capitol Sts. / Showing the Portion to be Acquired from the Capitol Square / for the Cutting off of Corner - Location of Proposed Entrance, 81-A-2, 1913, Dimensions: 17-1/2 x 39-1/4 in. - 44 x 100 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond Va.
  - Park - City of Richmond, Va. / William Byrd Park / Plan of Grass Plot Between / Davis Ave. and Park Driveway, 95-A-2, 1913, Dimensions: 11-1/4 x 44-1/2 in. - 8 x 113 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: Pencil, India ink, blue ink and green ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
    Drawn By: City Eng'r's Office / Richmond Va.
  - Park - Correct / Map / of / Properties of Wm. Byrd Realty Corporation / and / Stanhope Bolling / at / William Byrd Park, 44-C-2b, 1913, Dimensions: 19-3/4 x 34-1/4 in. - 50 x 87 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
  - Park - Plan - Elevation and Detail / of / Timber Grandstand / To be built around the Pump House / In the Athletic Field / at / William Byrd Park, 81-C-2, 1914, Dimensions: 28 x 36 in. - 71 x 91 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 37)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Va. / Aug 12 1914 / Approved Chas. E. Bolling / City Engineer
  - Park - Shield's Lake / William Byrd Park, 52-B-3c, 1914, Dimensions: 23 x 31 in. - 58 x 79 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: Pencil, India ink and colored inks on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 37)
    Drawn By: Fontaine Jones Asst. City Engineer
  - Park - Plan of / Fonticello Park / Fontecello Mineral Springs, Inc., 48-A-6a, 1914, Dimensions: 25-1/2 x 31 in. - 63 x 79 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
    Drawn By: Bolton, Clarke & Pratt / Incorporated / Civil Engineers. / Richmond, Va.
  - Park - Map of That Portion of Wm. Byrd Pak / Lying Southwest of Shields Lake / Showing Proposed Development, 84-C-2, 1914, Dimensions: 29-1/2 x 29-1/2 in. - 75 x 75 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: 1 pencil, India ink, and orange ink on linen, 1 pencil, India ink, and colored inks on heavy paper; Sheets: 2 (Folder 37)
    Drawn By: City Eng'r's Office / Richmond, Virginia / Map and Survey by / Fontaine Jones /Asst. City Eng'r
  - Park - Contour Map of a Portion of / Shield's Lake / Near Park Keeper's House / Showing Proposed Improvements, 52-B-3a,b, 1914, Dimensions: 26 x 28 in. - 66 x 71 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and colored inks on heavy paper; Sheets: 3 (Folder 37)
    Drawn By: City Eng'r's Office / Richmond, Va
  - Park - Plan of Property to be Acquired for / Riverside Park / at the South End and East Side of Pine St., 36-C-2b, 1914, Dimensions: 12-3/4 x 17-1/2 in. - 32 x 44 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink, red ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 44)
  - Park - Plan showing the area proposed to be taken for Fulton Park and a tabulated / statement of the several pieces of property embraced therein, 68-B-1, 1915, Dimensions: 31-3/4 x 25 in. - 80 x 63 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
  - Park - Shields Lake Wm. Byrd Park / Concrete Spillway in Upper Dam, 97-C-2, 1915, Dimensions: 28-1/2 x 32 in. - 73 x 81 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 37)
    Drawn By: City Eng'r's Office / Richmond, Va / Fontaine Jones / Ass't City Eng'r
  - Park - Profile of Granolithic Steps and Walkway from the National Cemetery Road Near Chimbarazo Park / to Fulton St. at Southern Ry. Crossing, 100-C-2, 1915, Dimensions: 20-1/4 x 57 in. - 52 x cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond: Virginia / Fontaine Jones / Ass't City Eng'r
  - Park - Plan of / Public Comfort Station to be / Erected in Rear of Courthouse / at Washington Square, So. Rich., 67-B-1, 1915, Dimensions: 19-1/2 x 32-1/2 in. - 49 x 83 cm.; Scale: 1" = 4'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 42)
  - Park - Map of a Portion of Chimborazo Park / Showing Sewer Leading From Park-house., 66-B-1, 1915, Dimensions: 19 x 26-3/4 in. - 48 x 68 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink, red ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 39)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Va / Fontaine Jones, Ass't City Eng'r
  - Park - Profile of Sidewalk on East Side / Twenty Third Street Between Franklin and Grace Streets, 102-A-2, 1915, Dimensions: 15-1/2 x 39 in. - 39 x 98 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
  - Park - Elevation and Section / Proposed Balustrade / Over the Spillway at / Shields Lake / William Byrd Park, 83-B-1, 1916, Dimensions: 19-3/4 x 31 in. - 50 x 79 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 2 (Folder 37)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Virginia / J.S. Potts, Jr. Asst. Engr.
  - Park - Plan for a Septic Tank and Map Showing / The Proposed Location Near Dam - Young's Pond, 107-A-2, 1916, Dimensions: 13 x 38-1/4 in. - 33 x 97 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 36)
  - Park - Map & Profile - Showing Survey for / Proposed Pipe Line to Relieve Over-Charged Sewers / in the Vicinity of B Street near Chestnut Road / William Byrd Park - Richmond, Virginia, 10165-B-1, 1917, Dimensions: 23-3/4 x 32-1/4 in. - 60 x 82 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 37)
  - Park - Proposed Drain to Prevent Slides / Chimborazo Park near Spring, 10462-B-1, 1918, Dimensions: 24 x 36 in. - 61 x 91 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and colored inks on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 39)
  - Park - Suggested Plan for Bath House Below Shield Lake Dam, 10926-A-6a, 1919, Dimensions: 1 x 46 in. - 48 x 117 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
    Drawn By: 'Office of Director of Public Works / Richmond, Va. / A. H. Harris A.E.
  - Park - Revised Plan Showing Toilets / for / Bath House / Shields Lake, 10926-A-6c, 1920, Dimensions: 15-3/4 x 20-1/2 in. - 40 x 52 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
  - Park - Proposed Change of Entrance to Capitol Square / 10th and Bank Streets, [No file number], 1920, Dimensions: 22-1/4 X 50-1/2 in. - 56 x 128 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 8)
  - Park - Revised Plan / of Entrance to Capitol Square / 12th and Bank Streets, [No file number], 1920, Dimensions: 29-1/2 x 41-1/2 in.- 75 x 105 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 8)
  - Park - Proposed Change of Entrance to Capitol Square / 12th and Bank Streets, 11012-D-16, 1920, Dimensions: 29-1/2 x 41-1/2 in.- 75 x 105 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 8)
  - Park - Plan of Bank Street / from / 9th to 12th / Showing / Widening On North Side Fifteen Feet, 11011-D-16, 1920, Dimensions: 30-1/2 x 105 in. - 77 x 267 cm.; Scale: 1" = 10'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and colored inks on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 9)
  - Park - Proposed Change of Entrance to Capitol Square / 9th and Bank Streets, [No file number], 1920, Dimensions: 22-1/4 x 45 in. - 56 x 114 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 8)
  - Park - Proposed Change of Entrance to Capitol Square / 12th and Franklin Streets, [No file number], 1920, Dimensions: 29-1/2 x 41-1/2 in.- 75 x 105 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 8)
  - Park - Typical Section through Bank Street, [No file number], 1920, Dimensions: 21-3/4 x 35-3/4 in. - 55 x 91 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 8)
  - Park - Office of Director of Public Works / Frame Bath House Shield Lake / Revised Plan of 75 Feet to be Built, 10926-A-6c, 1920, Dimensions: 22 x 37 in. - 56 x 94 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
    Drawn By: A. M. Harris A. E.
  - Park - Proposed Change of Entrance to Capitol Square / 11th and Bank Streets, [No file number], 1920, Dimensions:; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 8)
  - Park - Entrance Posts / To Be Used at / 10th and Bank, 11th and Bank and / 12th and Franklin Sts., [No file number], 1920, Dimensions: 18 x 16-1/2 in. - 46 x 47 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 8)
    Drawn By: Director of Public Works
  - Park - Proposed Change of Entrance to Capitol Square / 12th and Bank Streets, [No file number], 1921, Dimensions: 28-1/2 x 66 in. - 72 x 168 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, red ink, and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 9)
    Drawn By: Director of Public Works / Richmond, Va.
  - Park - Proposed Change to Entrance to Capitol Square / 10th and Bank Streets, [No file number], 1921, Dimensions: 29-1/2 x 41-1/2 in.- 75 x 105 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 9)
  - Park - Proposed Change to Entrance to Capitol Square / 11th and Bank Streets, [No file number], 1921, Dimensions: 29-1/2 x 41-1/2 in.- 75 x 105 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 9)
  - Park - Proposed Change of Entrance to Capitol Square / 9th and Bank Streets, [No file number], 1921, Dimensions: 28-1/2 x 66 in. - 72 x 168 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 9)
  - Park - Typical Section showing Proposed Granite Retaining Wall on / North Side of Bank St., [No file number], 1921, Dimensions: 19-1/2 x 29 in. - 50 x 74 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Pencil, red ink, and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 9)
  - Park - Culvert / for / Bryan Park, 11115-C-2, 1921, Dimensions: 24-3/4 x 37-1/4 in. - 63 x 94 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 36)
  - Park - Entrance at 12th & Bank Sts. and Entrance at 9th. & Bank Sts. [details of steps], [No file number], 1921, Dimensions: 10 x 16-1/2 in. - 25 x 42 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 9)
    Drawn By: Dept. of Public Works
  - Park - Club House for the / Byrd Park Club Incorporated / Richmond, Virginia, 11185-A-4, 1922, Dimensions: 18 x 24 in. - 46 x 61 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 6 (Folder 38)
  - Park - Richmond Stadium, Richmond, Virginia, [No file number], 1928, Dimensions: 91 1/2 x 60 1/2 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 9 (Folder 103)
    Drawn By: Lee, Smith, and Vandervoort/Architects & Engineers/ Richmond, Virginia/ Gavin Hadden/ New York City/Consulting Engineer
  - Park - Proposed Layout / of Approach to / Virginia War Memorial / in Byrd Park / and Suggested Treatment / for Immediate Surroundings, [No file number], 1931, Dimensions: 21 x 34 in. - 53 x 86 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: Pencil and watercolors on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 104)
    Drawn By: Ernest Gilbert; CD # 137.
  - Park - Plat of Part of Bellevue Park in Henrico / County Va. Showing Property of J. Lee Davis, D-46-a, 1932, Dimensions: 21-1/4 x 28 in. - 54 x 71 cm.; Scale: 1" = 60'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 46)
    Drawn By: T. Crawford Redd & Bros.
  - Park - Proposed / Richmond Stadium / Street Approaches, [No file number], ca.1928, Dimensions: 40 x 30-1/4 in. - 102 x 77 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil, India ink, and colored (watercolor?) washes on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 103)
    Drawn By: Lee, Smith, and Vandervoort / Richmond, Virginia
  - Park - Approximate Quantities [amount of excavation in modifying entrances to Capitol Square], [No file number], n.d, Dimensions: 7 x 12-1/2 in. - 18 x 32 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 9)
    Drawn By: [Director of Public Works / Richmond, Va.]
  - Park - Dam / Joseph Bryan Memorial Park / Details of Arrangements for Splash Boards, 41-B-3, n.d., Dimensions: 23-3/4 x 25 in. - 60 x 63 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen graph paper with pencil notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 36)
  - Park - [Plan of Monroe Park], 5-B-5, n.d., Dimensions: 31 x 29 in. -79 x 74 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil, India ink, and colored inks on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 43)
  - Park - [Section of dam and drainage piping], 29-C-3, n.d., Dimensions: 35-1/2 x 50 in. - 90 x 127 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
  - Park - [Plan of vaults under the pavilion at Chimbarazo Park (?)], 30-B-2, n.d., Dimensions: 19-1/4 x 24-1/4 in. - 49 x 62 xcm.; Scale: None; Media: 1 pencil, India ink, and red ink on cloth-backed paper, 1 India ink and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 2 (Folder 39)
  - Park - [Study for roadways in Libbie Hill Park below the monument], 41-B-5, n.d., Dimensions: 19-1/2 x 31-1/4 in. - 50 x 79 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink, red ink, pencil, and colored crayon on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 41)
  - Park - [Proposed location of pavilion], 34-B-4, n.d., Dimensions: 21-1/4 x 18-1/4 in. - 54 x 46 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
  - Park - Addition to Bath House / Shields Lake, 10926-A-6, n.d., Dimensions: 24-3/4 x 34-1/4 in. - 63 x 87 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
  - Park - Railing to Steps from College / to Jail Alley on Marshall, 37-C-3, n.d., Dimensions: 15-1/2 x 14-1/4 in. - 39 x 36 cm.; Scale: Full scale; Media: Pencil and India ink on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
  - Park - Proposed / Civic Center / for / Richmond / Virginia, Y-3302, n.d., Dimensions: 16 x 27 in. - 41 x 69 cm.; Scale: 1" = 200'; Media: India ink and green ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
    Drawn By: Drawn by W. F. Beaman
  - Park - [Plan of steps from Franklin Street to Main Street], 68-A-1, n.d., Dimensions: 15 x 41-3/4 in. - 38 x 106 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
  - Park - [Calculations for excavations at intersection of Park Ave., Meadow St., Ivy St., and Park St.], 22-D-3, n.d., Dimensions: 13-1/2 x 22 in. - 34 x 56 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and ink on graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
  - Park - [Plan of Monroe Park], 54-A-2a,b, n.d., Dimensions: 15 x 11-1/2 in. - 38 x 29 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen with pencil notations; Sheets: 2 (Folder 43)
  - Park - Pavilion at Chimborazo Park, 6-A-3, n.d., Dimensions: 24 x 31 in. - 61 x 79 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil, India ink, and colored inks on linen; Sheets: 5 (Folder 39)
    Drawn By: Edgerton S. Rogers, Architect / Richmond, VA.
  - Park - Plat of a Portion of / Joseph Bryan Park, 107-A-2, n.d., Dimensions: 12 x 22-1/2 in. - 30 x 57 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 36)
  - Park - Map of Fountain in Monroe Square / Showing Walks Adjacent, 54-A-2b, n.d., Dimensions: 17 x 18-1/2 in. - 43 x 47 cm.; Scale: 1" = 10'; Media: Pencil and India ink on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 43)
  - Park - Plan / of Council Chamber / Hill, 1-B-5, n.d., Dimensions: 23-3/4 x 30 in. - 60 x 76 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil and India ink with colored ink washes and pencil notations on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 100)
  - Park - [Elevation of entrance gate for Joseph Bryan Park], 38-A-6, n.d., Dimensions: 10 x 16-3/4 in. - 26 x 43 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Scoring and pencil on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 36)
  - Park - Plan / for / Granolithic Steps / Jefferson Park, 7-C-3, n.d., Dimensions: 26 x 37 in. - 66 x 94 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 92)
  - Park - Working plan for the improvement of 'Gamble Hill,' Richmond, Va., 23-B-5, n.d., Dimensions: 22-3/4 x 28-3/4 in. - 58 x 73 cm.; Scale: [1" = 40']; Media: Pencil, India ink, and colored ink washes on heavy paper with cloth backing; Sheets: 1 (Folder 40)
    Drawn By: By Wm. Brackenridge
  - Park - [Diagram of proposed walkway modification], 5-B-5, n.d., Dimensions: 20-3/4 x 14-3/4 in. - 53 x 38 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink, red ink, and blue ink, on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 43)
    Drawn By: S. Ed. Bates